## **Fima Treiger**

## **Full Stack Developer**

Ra'anana | 058-700-0568 | fima1fim@hotmail.com <u>Github</u> | <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Portfolio</u>

#### SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in JavaScript based programming, postgreSQL database management and node.js Back-End, focused on Front-End creation of web apps using React and Redux for state management. Ability to learn new tools and frameworks depending on the companies or clients' needs, with an aptitude for problem-solving issues under pressure, excellent communication skills worker to management, flexible with moment to moment changes on projects, being able to re-focus to complete any task at hand under strict deadlines.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap + React-Bootstrap, Javascript [ES6+], React, Redux, PostgreSQL, Node.js, Express.js

#### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

## Cardmem- Github | Demo

Card memory game created with vanilla JavaScript and pure DOM manipulation deployed on Netlify

- Pure CSS, HTML and JavaScript
- Score keeping with victory condition
- Mismatch turns over all cards and resets the score

### Project NASA - Github | Demo

NASA API single page application created with React.js and React-Router, deployed on Netlify

- Multiple NASA API's used for fetching information and images
- Rover page allows to generate image baches for NASA's images from Mars captured by their rover

### D&D Pal - Github | Demo

Full-Stack D&D companion app created with React, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, Bcrypt.js for password hashing and KNEX to connect with PostgreSQL, React-Router with protected routes, Multer for image upload, using D&D5e API

- PostgreSQL databases connected and manipulated through node.js with dotenv and knex.js
- Password hashed on registration with Bcrypt.js, on login compared and authenticates the user to view protected routes on successful login with React-Router. Deployed on Heroku with a Database.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# HVAC Technician and Electrician Mashay Central, Israel 03/2019 - 11/2021

Diagnosed and repaired HVAC systems of all kinds

## Reserves NCO

IDF

Central, Israel 08/2017 - 11/2017

- Prepared and installed military radio and communication equipment
- Led and instructed enlisted soldiers

#### **EDUCATION**

## Full Stack Web Development, JavaScript program Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp Tel-Aviv, Israel 12/2021 - 02/2022

#### Self-Learning

Multiple udemy courses from Zero to Mastery on JavaScript, React and Node

08/2021 - present

LANGUAGES

Languages (English - fluent, Hebrew - native, Russian - fluent.)